A Guide to the Old Dominion University Photograph Collection 1930s-1990s
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Old Dominion University Photograph Collection 1930-1990s
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
RG 32
120 clamshell photo boxes; 51 linear feet.
Administrative Information
Access
The collection is open to researchers without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred to Special Collections from the University Relations office and University Photographer.
Scope and Content Information
This collection includes a variety of photographs covering the history of the University from 1930 to the 1990s. Photographic subjects include, students, faculty, administrators, academic departments, buildings and grounds, events, sororities, fraternities, sports, convocations, musical and theatrical performances, guest speakers, and student organizations.
Arrangement
Arrangement
The collection is organized into series chronologically by decade. Within each series the photographs are organized alphabetically by subject.
Organization
The collection is divided into the following series: Series I: 1930s (Box 1); Series II: 1940s (Boxes 2-3); Series III: 1950s (Boxes 4-26); Series IV: 1960s (Boxes 27-54); Series V: 1970s (Boxes 55-78); Series VI: Negatives (Boxes 79-83); Series VII: Slides Relating to ODU History (Box 84); Series VIII: Transparencies and Postcards (Box 85); Series IX: 1980s (Boxes 86-97); Series X: 1990s (Boxes 98-120).
Contents List
- 1930s
  - Administration-College of William and Mary (I) (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administration-College of William and Mary (II) (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Athletics-Baseball (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Athletics-Basketball (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Athletics-Football (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Athletics-Track (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Forman Field, Stadium (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Gray's Pharmacy (1926) (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hampton Boulevard (1926) (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Faculty (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Student Life (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 12)
  - University Administration (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1940s
  - Athletics-Archery (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Athletics-Basketball (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Athletics-Basketball, Women's (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Athletics-Cheerleaders (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Athletics-Field Hockey (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Athletics-Lacrosse (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Athletics-Swimming (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Athletics-Track (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Foreman Field, Stadium (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Technical Institute (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Faculty (I) (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Faculty (II) (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Military (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Non-Academic Staff (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Other Events-Open House (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Other Events-Tree Planting (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Student Life (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Student Life-High Hat (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Student Organizations-Biology Club (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Omega Phi (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Student Organizations-Di Gamma (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Student Organizations-Drama Club (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Student Organizations-French Club (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Student Organizations-Interclub Council (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Student Organizations-Kappa Sigma Kappa (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Student Organizations-Phalanx Club (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Student Organizations-Sigma Epsilon Pi (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Student Organizations-Student Government (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Student Portraits (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Theater-"The Male Animal" (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Theater-"You Can't Take It With You" (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 3)
  - University Administration (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Academic Departments-Art (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Academic Departments-Chemistry (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Academic Departments-Engineering (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Academic Departments-Music (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Academic Departments-Nursing (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (I) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (II) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (III) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (IV) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (V) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (VI) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (VII) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (VIII) (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 17)
- 1950s
  - Alumni (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Activities (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Convocations (I) (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Convocations (II) (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Convocations-Judge Harold R. Medina (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Honors and Awards (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Military (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Non-Academic Staff (I) (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Non-Academic Staff (II) (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Non-Academic Staff (III) (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Theater (I) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Theater (II) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Theater-"Pirates of Penzance" (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Theater-"Geraldine and the White Robe" (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Theater-"Tiger at the Gates" (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Theater-Evening College Drama Club (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 6)
  - University Administration (I) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 7)
  - University Administration (II) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 8)
  - University Administration (III) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 9)
  - University Administration (IV) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 10)
  - University Administration (V) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 11)
  - University Administration (VI) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Academic Departments-Art (I) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Academic Departments-Art (II) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Academic Departments-Art (III) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Academic Departments-Biology (I) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Academic Departments-Biology (II) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Academic Departments-Business/Distributive Education/Merchandising (I) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Academic Departments-Business/Distributive Education/Merchandising (II) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Academic Departments-Business/Distributive Education/Merchandising (III) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Academic Departments-Classroom View (I) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Academic Departments-Classroom View (II) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Academic Departments-Dental Hygiene (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Education Division (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Academic Departments-English (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Academic Departments-History (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Academic Departments-Industrial Arts (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Academic Departments-Laboratory View (I) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Academic Departments-Laboratory View (II) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Academic Departments-Music (I) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Academic Departments-Music (II) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Academic Departments-Music (III) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Academic Departments-Music (IV) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Academic Departments-Music (V) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Academic Departments-Nursing (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (I) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (II) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (III) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (IV) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (V) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (VI) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (VII) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (VIII) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 14)
  - School of Social Work (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Academic Departments-Speech (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Speech Center (I) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Speech Center (II) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (I) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (II) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (III) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (IV) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (V) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (VI) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (VII) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (VIII) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (IX) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (X) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (XI) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (XII) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (XIII) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (XIV) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (XV) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (XVI) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (XVII) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (XVIII) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (XIX) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (XX) (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Athletics-Archery (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Athletics-Baseball (I) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Athletics-Baseball (II) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Athletics-Baseball (III) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Athletics-Basketball (I) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Athletics-Basketball (II) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Athletics-Basketball (III) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Athletics-Basketball (IV) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Athletics-Basketball (V) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Athletics-Basketball (VI) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Athletics-Basketball (VII) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Athletics-Basketball (VIII) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Athletics-Basketball (IX) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Athletics-Basketball (X) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Athletics-Basketball (XI) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Athletics-Basketball, Women's (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Athletics-Cheerleaders (I) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Athletics-Cheerleaders (II) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Athletics-Field Hockey (I) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Athletics-Field Hockey (II) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Athletics-Field Hockey (III) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Athletics-Field Hockey (IV) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Athletics-Swimming (I) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Athletics-Swimming (II) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Athletics-Swimming (III) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Athletics-Swimming, Women's (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Athletics-Tennis (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Athletics-Track (I) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Athletics-Track (II) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Athletics-Track (III) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Athletics-Track (IV) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Athletics-Track (V) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Athletics-Track (VI) (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Athletics-Wrestling (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds (I) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds (II) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Buildings and Grounds (III) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds (IV) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds (V) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds (VI) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds (VII) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds (VIII) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds (IX) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Administration Building (I) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Administration Building (II) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Administration Building (III) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Administration Building (Interior) (IV) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Administration Building (Interior) (V) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Barracks (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Foreman Field Stadium (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hughes Library (I) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hughes Library (II) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hughes Library (III) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hughes Library (IV) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hughes Library (V) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hughes Library (VI) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds-New Science Building (I) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds-New Science Building (II) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Science Building (I) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Science Building (II) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Science Building (III) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Science Building (IV) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Science Building (V) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Technical Institute (I) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Technical Institute (II) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Technical Institute (III) (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Faculty (I) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Faculty (II) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Faculty (III) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Faculty (IV) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Faculty (V) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Faculty (VI) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Faculty (VII) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Faculty (VIII) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Faculty (IX) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Faculty (X) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Faculty (XI) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Faculty (XII) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Faculty (XIII) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Faculty (XIV) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Faculty (XV) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Faculty (XVI) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Activities (I) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Activities (II) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Activities (III) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Activities (IV) (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Musical Performances (I) (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Musical Performances (II) (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Musical Performances-"H.M.S. Pinafore," 1950 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Musical Performances-"The Mikado," 1950 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Musical Performances-Christmas Chorus, 1950 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Musical Performances-Christmas Program, 1951 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Musical Performances-"The Messiah," 1951 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Musical Performances-"Pirates of Penzance," 1951-1952 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Musical Performances-The Chorus, March 24, 1952 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Musical Performances-"Trial by Jury," 1952 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Musical Performances-"La Serva Padrona," 1952 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Musical Performances-"Down In The Valley," 1952 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Musical Performances-Madrigals, 1952-1953 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Musical Performances-"Amahl and The Night Visitors," 1953 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Musical Performances-Blanche Thebom, 1953 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Musical Performances-Gianni Schicci, 1953 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Musical Performances-"The Devil and Daniel Webster," 1953-1954 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Musical Performances-"The Chocolate Soldier," 1954 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Musical Performances-Concert Series/Variety Show, 1954 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Musical Performances-"The Messiah"-Christmas, 1954 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Musical Performances-The Madrigal Singers, 1954-1955 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Musical Performances-The Chorus, 1954-1955 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Musical Performances-"The Marriage of Figarro," April 30, 1955 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Musical Performances-"The Well," 1955 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Musical Performances-The Madrigal Singers, 1955-1956 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Musical Performances-The Chorus, 1955-1956 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Musical Performances-College Band, 1956 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Musical Performances-College Choir, 1956 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Musical Performances-"Hansel and Gretel," 1956 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Musical Performances-Chamber Music Concert, 1956 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Musical Performances-"The Medium", 1956 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Musical Performances-Student Recitals, 1956 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Musical Performances-The Madrigal Singers, 1956-1957 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Musical Performances-The Chorus, 1956-1957 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Musical Performances-The College Band, 1956-1957 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Musical Performances-Concert Series, 1957 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "La Boheme", 1957 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 15)
  - The Concert Choir, 1957-1958 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Musical Performances-"Carmen," 1958 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Musical Performances-Contemporary Chamber Music Concert, 1958 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Musical Performances-"Oklahoma," (I) 1958 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Musical Performances-"Oklahoma," (II) 1958 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Musical Performances-Student Recitals, 1958 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Musical Performances-College Band, 1958 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Other Events-Aqua Fantasia Water Show (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Other Events-Armed Forces Week (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Other Events-Blood Drive (I) (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Other Events-Blood Drive (II) (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Other Events-Book Drive (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Other Events-Camellia Show (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Other Events-Civil Service Placement (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Other Events-1930 Class Reunion (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Other Events-C+P Telephone Films (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Hughes Library (I) (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Hughes Library (II) (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Other Events-Dedication: New Science Building (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Other Events-Distributive Education (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Other Events-Eddie Cantor Appearance, April 3, 1950 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Other Events-Education Department (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Other Events-Education of Faculty Children, 1958 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Other Events-English Major Day (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Other Events-Executive Development Conference (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Other Events-Federal Career Day (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Other Events-Future Business Leaders of America (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Other Events-Leonardo Da Vinci Exhibit (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Other Events-Mathematics Lecture (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Other Events-N.A.T.O. Seminar (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Other Events-Second N.A.T.O. Seminar (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Other Events-Office Manager's Conference (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Other Events-Pilot Relays (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Other Events-P.T.A Leadership Training Institute (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Other Events-Showboat Minstrel (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Other Events-Silver Anniversary (I) (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Other Events-Silver Anniversary (II) (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Other Events-Silver Anniversary (III) (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Other Events-Tax Conference (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Other Events-New Telephone System (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Other Events-Tidewater Conference on Federal Taxation (I) (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Other Events-Tidewater Conference on Federal Taxation (II) (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Other Events-Tidewater Public Schools Supervisors Meeting (Box-folder Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Student Life, 42 Folders (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 1-Box 19, Folder 23:)
  - Student Life-"Campus Capers" (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Student Life-Chieftain (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Student Life-High Hat (I) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Student Life-High Hat (II) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Student Life-High Hat (III) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Student Life-High Hat (IV) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Student Life-Inoculation (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Student Life-Presidential Elections, 1952 and 1956 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Student Life-Registration (I) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Student Life-Registration (II) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Student Life-Student Government Elections (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Student Life-Voyager (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Student Life-WMTI (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Student Life-Bert Harrell and Marion Carroll in old Norfolk Division Dance Class (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Student Organizations (I) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Student Organizations (II) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Student Organizations (III) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Student Organizations (IV) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Student Organizations (V) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Student Organizations-Alpha Kappa Psi (I) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Student Organizations-Alpha Kappa Psi (II) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Student Organizations-Alpha Omega Phi (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Student Organizations-American Society of Civil Engineers (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Student Organizations-Baptist Student Union (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 24)